A Guide to the Clarence L. Townes Jr. Papers, 1944-1988
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Richmond Renaissance 1982-1987
  - Market Analysis A Festival Marketplace in Downtown Richmond, Virginia Melvin R. Levine and Associates, inc. October 1982 (Box 23)
  - Marketing 1987 (Box 23)
  - Newspaper Clippings, Brochure on Waterside, other clippings n.d. (Box 23)
  - Notes (Clarence L. Townes) n.d. 1982 (Box 23)
  - Small Business Administration/503 Loan Program n.d. 1983 (Box 24)
  - Statement of Goals 1983, 1984 (Box 24)
  - Tobacco Row Associates-Development Project n.d. 1985-1986 (Box 24)
  - Tourism Subcommittee 1982 (Box 24)
  - Trolley-Downtown Shuttle Correspondence, Report 1982 (Box 24)
  - Visitors Center-John D. Hunt-Tourism study, Correspondence n.d. 1982 (Box 24)
  - Brown's Island Walkway n.d. 1983, Oversize
  - Budget/Contract with City of Richmon-Correspondence, notes 1983, Oversize
  - CLC Taskforce n.d. 1983 (Box 24)
  - McGuire, Woods, Battle and Boothe-Richmond Still Making History-Service Mark 1987, Oversize
  - Newspaper Articles on Richmond Renaissance- Richmond Times Dispatch, Richmond Newsleader 1982, Oversize
  - Richmond Banner Display Program 1986, Oversize
- Publications 1961-1973
  - How to Get Publicity: A Guide for Republican Publicity Chairmen n.d. (Box 25)
  - Comprehensive Program of Health Protection, for the Employees of Republican National Committee n.d. (Box 25)
  - Republican Clubwoman's Leadership Manual National Federation of Republican Women n.d. (Box 25)
  - Practical Guide to Registration and Voter Drives n.d. (2 copies) (Box 25)
  - How to Present a Public Program College Republican National Committee n.d. (Box 25)
  - Student Canvas Manual College Republican National Committee n.d. (Box 25)
  - Statewide Leadership Memo College Republican National Committee n.d. (Box 25)
  - How to Prepare a Club Newsletter College Republican National Committee n.d. (Box 25)
  - How to Budget and Finance Your Club College Republican National Committee n.d. (Box 25)
  - New Student Politics College Republican National Committee n.d. (Box 25)
  - Report of the Committee on Big City Politics by Ray Bliss, Chairman, Republican State Central and Executive Committee of Ohio, presented before RNC Meeting June (2 copies) 1961 (Box 25)
  - Young Republican Organization Guide 1962 (Box 25)
  - 1962 Congressional Vote Statistics Republican Congressional Committee 1963 (Box 25)
  - 1962 Elections, A Summary Report with Supporting Tables RNC 1963 (Box 25)
  - Republican Challenge Republican Campaign Committee for Richmond and Henrico County 1963 (Box 25)
  - Republican State Convention, June 12-13 1964, John Marshall Hotel, Richmond, VA-Souvenir Program 1964 (Box 25)
  - Election 64-A Rippon Society Report 1964 (Box 25)
  - 1964 Elections: A Summary Report with Supporting Tables RNC 1965 (Box 25)
  - Balance of Payments, The Gold Drain and Your Dollar 1965 (Box 25)
  - Republican FACT Book 1966 Election Campaign 1966 (Box 25)
  - Report by the Chairman 1966 to the RNC 1967 (Box 25)
  - Confidential For Republican Ears Only...Dial VI-1966 for Victory in November-RNC 1966 (Box 25)
  - 1966 Elections: A Summary Report with Supporting Tables RNC 2copies 1967 (Box 25)
  - Ways to Win RNC 1967 (Box 25)
  - Permanent Roll of Delegates and Alternate Delegates to Republican National Convention 1968 (Box 25)
  - Telephone Directory and Guide Republican National Convention (Box 25)
  - Republican Platform 1968 (Box 25)
  - 1968 Spring Catalogue of Republican Campaign Materials RNC 1968 (Box 25)
  - 1968 Convention Delegate Counter 1968 (Box 25)
  - Chairman's Report-1968 To the RNC 1969 (Box 25)
  - Richard Nixon on Bridges to Human Dignity 1968 (Box 25)
  - 10 Ways you can help Richard Nixon United Citizens for Nixon 1968 (Box 25)
  - Afro-American Voter January-Febreuary (Memorial Edition to Joseph A. Clarke) 1969 (Box 25)
  - Afro-American Voter March-April (A Look at President Nixon's Domestic Program and how it effects black America) 1969 (Box 25)
  - 1st Annual Dinner-Dance, New York Caucus National Council of Concern Afro-American Republicans 1969 (Box 25)
  - Republican national Committee Program for the Black Community 1969 (Box 25)
  - Listening Program-RNC 1970 (Box 25)
  - History of the Republican Party (Box 25)
  - Republican December 1970 (Box 25)
  - 1968 Elections, a summary Report with supporting tables 1970 (Box 25)
  - Political Profiles of the States 2 copies 1970 (Box 25)
  - Mission 70's Manual and Workbook 1970 (Box 25)
  - Republican Almanac 1973 (Box 25)
  - African American Voter-Memorial Edition to Joseph A. Clarke Jan.-Feb. 1969 (Box 25)
  - African American Voter-A Look at President Nixon's Domestic Program and How it Effects Black Americans March-April 1969 (Box 25)
  - Practical guide to Registration and Voter Drives (Box 25)
  - GOP Leader's Manual 1966 (Box 25)
  - You Can Go to College Congressman William Roth (Box 25)
  - History of the Republican Party 1854-1970 (Box 25)
  - Rippon Forum May 1965 (Box 25)
  - New Directors v.1 #1, 3, 5 1968 (Box 25)
  - Republican Congressional Committee Newsletter #21, 23, 25, 26 1969 (Box 25)
  - GOP Nationalities News v.4 #1 January 1974 (Box 25)
  - Monday RNC July 21, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Monday RNC Sept. 8, 1969 (Box 25)
  - Souvenir Journal-Dr. Lawrence C. Arnett Republican Club, 56th A.D. Regular Republican Organization, New York, Thirteenth Annual Dance 1969 (Box 25)
  - Federal Regional Council-Region V Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 26)
  - Population Charactericstics, Negro Population March, Dept. of Commerce (3 copies) 1967 (Box 26)
  - Civil Rights Digest- A Quarterly of the U.s. Commission on Civil Rights Winter 1969 (Box 26)
  - Civil Rights Digest-A Quarterly of the U.S. Commission on Civil Rights Winter 1970 (Box 26)
  - Directory of Privat Programs for Minority Business Enterprise, August 1969 (Box 26)
  - Work Attitiudes of Disadvantaged Black Men Dept. of Labor 1972 (Box 26)
  - U.S. Labor Force: Projections to 1985 Dept. of Labor 1970 (Box 26)
  - Geographic Profile of Employment and Unemployment, 1971 Dept. of Labor 1972 (Box 26)
  - Unemployment by Region and in Largest States Dept. of Labor 1970 (Box 26)
  - Operation Breakthrough: Questions and Answers June 1970 (Box 26)
  - Fair Housing Laws and Other Federal Civil Rights Laws and Executive Orders Relating to the Programs of the Dept. of Housing and Urban Development 1969 (Box 26)
  - Our American Government- What Is It? How Does it Function? U.S. Senate 1963 (Box 26)
  - Interviewer's Handbook for Selection and Referral to Training and Placement Dept. of Labor 1969 (Box 26)
  - Federal Aid to States Fiscal Year 1971 Dept. of Treasury 1972 (Box 26)
  - 1970 Census Tracts-Norfolk-Portsmouth, Virginia Dept. of Commerce 1972 (Box 26)
  - 1970 Census Tracts-Lynchburg, Virginia Dept. of Commerce 1972 (Box 26)
  - 1970 Census Tracts-Roanoke, Virginia Dept. of Commerce 1972 (Box 26)
  - 1970 Census Tracts-Newport News-Hampton, Virginia Dept. of Commerce 1972 (Box 26)
  - 1970 Census of Population-Virginia July 1970 (Box 26)
  - Technical Analysis Division: Project Summaries 1967-1969 Dept. of Commerce 1970 (Box 26)
  - Comprehensive Planning Assistance Handbook I Managing a Grant March 1969-Housing and Urban Development 1969 (Box 26)
  - Comprehensive Planning Assistance Handbook II Mananging a Grant March 1969-Housing and Urban Development 1969 (Box 26)
  - Cabinet Committee on Opportunities for Spanish Speaking People-A New Era 1970 (Box 26)
  - Better Communities, HUD Programs to Improve Community Housing and Urban Development 1969 (Box 26)
  - Multistate Regionalism Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations 1972 (Box 26)
  - Negro Employment in the South Volume 1: The Houston Labor Market Dept. of Labor (Box 26)
  - High Impact Anti-Crime Program Dept. of Justice 1972 (Box 26)
  - U.S. Manpower in the 1970s Dept. of Labor 1970 (Box 26)
  - Political Participation U.S. Commission on Civil Rights 1968 (Box 26)
  - HUD News July 1971 (Box 26)
  - Federal Installations and Equal Housing Opportunity U.S. Commission on Civil Rights 1970 (Box 26)
  - Labor Management Policies for State and Local Government Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations 1969 (Box 26)
  - Performance of Urban Functions: Local and Areawide Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations (2 copies) 1963 (Box 26)
  - Our Flag U.S. Congress 1967 (Box 26)
  - Factual Campaign Information Senate Library 1970 (Box 26)
  - Equal Opportunity-A Bibliography of Research on Equal Opportunity in Housing Compiled by the U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development Library 1969 (Box 26)
  - Mexican Americans: A Bibliography U.S. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development 1970 (Box 26)
  - Social and Economic Status of Negroes in the United States 1969 (Box 26)
  - Services for Families Living in Public Housing Part II A Selected Bibliography Committee on Use of Program Resources of the Joint Task Force on Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 26)
  - Services and Housing 1965 (Box 26)
  - Technical Proposal in Response to RFP-A.I.D. Supported Operational Personnel for Africa Agency for International Development Bureau for Africa, Dept. of State 1970 (Box 26)
  - Fair Housing Law and other Federal Civil Rights Law and Executive Orders Relating to the Programs of the U.S. Department of Housing and Urban Development 1969 (Box 26)
  - U.S. Department of Health Education and Welfare Fiscal Year Budget 1973 (Box 26)
  - Manpower Research and Development Projects U.S. Department of Labor Manpower Administration 1971 (Box 26)
  - Handbook for Interlocal Agreements and Contracts Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations 1967 (Box 26)
  - State-Local Finances and Suggested Legislation Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations 1971 (Box 26)
  - New Minority Enterprises-Community Relations Service Dept. of Justice 1969 (Box 26)
  - Rental Housing for Lower Income Families Dept. of Housing and Urban Development 1968 (Box 26)
  - Policy and Supporting Positions Committee on Post Office and Civil Service House of Represenatives 1968 (Box 26)
  - Management Assistance Program 2 Personnel Dept. of Housing and Urban Develpoment n.d. (Box 26)
  - U.S. Department of Transportation-Facts and Functions 1971 (Box 26)
  - Grant Assistance Programs of the EPA 1972 (Box 26)
  - Report of an Investigation into an Educational Dilemma 1970 (Box 26)
  - Social and Economic Status of Negroes in the U.S., 1970 Dept. of Commerce 1971 (Box 26)
  - Nondiscrimination in Federally-Assisted Programs Dept. of Housing and Urban Development 1971 (Box 26)
  - Differentials and Overlaps in Annual Earnings of Blacks and Whites Dept. of Labor 1971 (Box 26)
  - Construction Manpower Needs by 1980 Dept. of Labor 1971 (Box 26)
  - Index-Federal Civil Rights Enforcement Effort of a Report of the United States Commission on Civil Rights (Box 26)
  - Mountfour Point Marine Association Fifth Annual Convention Atlanta Host Chapter, U.S. Marine Corps 1969 (Box 26)
  - Congressional Quarterly Special Report on 1964 Presidential Election 1964 (Box 26)
  - Congressional Quarterly June 20, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Congressional Quarterly June 27, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Civil Rights Under Federal Programs-An Analysis of Title VI U.S. Commission on Civil Rights, January 1965 (Box 26)
  - We the Black People of the United States U.S. Dept. of Commerce (Box 26)
  - Federal Aid Control System Handbook Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 26)
  - Various Office of Economic Opportunity publications (Box 26)
  - Outlook U.S. Dept. of Commerce Sept. 1969 (Box 26)
  - Outlook U.S. Dept. of Commerce Nov. 1969 (Box 26)
  - Outlook U.S. Dept. of Commerce Dec. 1969 (Box 26)
  - Outlook U.S. Dept. of Commerce Feb. 1970 (Box 26)
  - Franchise Company for Equal Opportunity in Business U.S. Dept. of Commerce (Box 26)
  - Building Minority Enterprise Office of Minority Business Enterprise (Box 26)
  - Special Catalog of Federal Assistance Programs for Minority Business Enterprise Office of Economic Opportunity (Box 26)
  - Congressional Directory March 1969 (Box 27)
  - Changing Characteristics-Negro Population Dept. of Commerce (Box 27)
  - State Poll Tax List 1963 (Box 27)
  - Open or Closed Suburbs: Corporate Location and the Urban Crisis Suburban Action Institute 1971 (Box 27)
  - Urban Crisis and the Ghetto System: A Program for Grass-Roots Action National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing 1966 (Box 26)
  - War on Hunger: A Report from the Agency for International Development January 1968 (Box 27)
  - War on Hunger: A Report from the Agency for International Development January 1970 (Box 27)
  - War on Hunger: A Report from the Agency for International Development July 1970 (Box 27)
  - How to Break up the Racial Ghetto National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing 1965 (Box 27)
  - Application for Funding Under Section 6 Emergency Employment Act of 1971 City of East St. Louis, Illinois 1971 (Box 27)
  - Proposal to Norfolk Model City Agency Tidewater Area Minority Contractors Association Inc. 1970 1970 (Box 27)
  - Proposal to Small Business Administration Tidewater Area Minority Contractors Assciation Inc. 1971 (Box 27)
  - Proposal to Small Business Administration Supplement Tidewater Area Minority Contractors Association Inc. n.d. (Box 27)
  - Not Black, Not White but People n.d. (Box 27)
  - President's-Alumni Issue Virginia Union University October 1972 (Box 27)
  - Headstart on Reading by Dr. Ruth Strickland 1969 (Box 27)
  - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation and Bedford-Stuyvesant D and S Corporation and Subsidary Company-Annual Report 1968 (Box 27)
  - Neighborhoods: Where Human Relations Begin Southern Regional Council 1967 (Box 27)
  - Fair Housing Handbook-American Friends Service Committee and the National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing 1964 (Box 27)
  - Guide to Federal Low & Moderate-Income Housing and Community Development Programs National Urban Coalition 1970 (Box 27)
  - Cambridge School of Weston n.d. (Box 27)
  - Economic Data Summary Chesterfield County 1970 (Box 27)
  - Technical Proposal for a Planning Model for Intergrated Addict Rehabilitation Manpower Training Programs Bay Tech Associates Inc. n.d. (Box 27)
  - Urban Transportation: Minority Mobility in the 1970s Howard University School of Social Work-Urban Mass Transportation Administration Conference 1972 (Box 27)
  - National Black Economic Development Conference 1969 (Box 27)
  - Dimensions of Poverty in North Carolina by Michael P. Brooks-The North Carolina Fund June 1964 (Box 27)
  - Southwide Conference of Black Elected Officials-1968-The Voter Education Project Southern Regional Council, Inc. 1969 (Box 27)
  - Virginia Statewide Conference of Black Elected Officials, Bibliography 1969 (Box 27)
  - European Community February no. 131 1970 (Box 27)
  - Voting Behavior of Houston Negoes (A Study of Political Motivations and Voter Influences) by Henry Allen Bullock, Professor of Sociology, Texas Southern University 1964 (Box 27)
  - Facts Presented by the Virginia Education Association Legislative Committee in Support of its 1965-1966 Legislative Program 1965 (Box 27)
  - Manual for Speading Away(a reading program) n.d. (Box 27)
  - Decade of SCLC n.d. (Box 27)
  - National Roster of Black Elected Officials February 1970 (Box 27)
  - Crescent Official Organ of the Phi Beta Sigma Fraternity, Inc.-50th Anniversary 1964 (Box 27)
  - Highlights and Proceedings-National Bankers Association Convention 1968 (Box 27)
  - Calendar-B.P.U.M.-Economic Development Corporation 1974-1975 (Box 27)
  - Ways and Means Handbook Sperry and Hutchinson Company 1964 (Box 27)
  - Membership Handbook Sperry and Hutchinson Company 1966 (Box 27)
  - How Classroom Desegregation Will Work by Henry E. Garret n.d. (Box 27)
  - Ill-Housed League of Women Voters n.d. (Box 27)
  - Issues for Study in Cable Communications Alfred P. Sloan Foundation 1970 (Box 27)
  - Crisis Without Violence-Story of a Hot Summer by Alexander F. Miller n.d. (Box 27)
  - Black Candidates: Southern Campaign Experiences by Julian Bond 2 copies 1968 (Box 27)
  - Civil Rights Movement Re-Examined A Philip Randolph Educational Fund n.d. (Box 27)
  - Three Essays by Bayard Rustin-Myths of the Black Revolt, The Role of the Negro Middle Class, The Ballot Box and the Union Card A. Philip Randolph Institute 1969 (Box 27)
  - Community Corporations and Neighborhood Control by Howard W. Hallman-Center for Governmental Studies 1970 (Box 27)
  - Report of ActivitiesS and H Foundation, Inc. 1970 (Box 27)
  - Publicity Handbood Sperry and Hutchinson Co. 1972 (Box 27)
  - Public Affairs Handbook-A Guide to Achieving Good Government Sperry and Hutchinson Company (Box 27)
  - How the National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Began by Mary White Ovington-NAACP (Box 27)
  - Proceedings of the Forty-Eighth Annual Session of the National Insurance Association 1968 (Box 27)
  - Guide to Federal Low and Moderate Income Housing and Community Development Programs National Urban Coalition (2 copies) (Box 27)
  - Federal Information Exchange System(handbook) November 1968 (Box 27)
  - Turning Point Urban America Inc. 1968 (Box 27)
  - National Enviroment Foundation-A Brighter World Environment Through Enlightenment n.d. (Box 27)
  - Crescent Fall Issue Phi Beta Sigma Fraternity Inc. 1969 (Box 27)
  - Attack New York State Narcotic Addiction Control Commission 1969 (Box 27)
  - Voting is People Power League of Women Voters 1967 (Box 27)
  - Atlanta Elections of 1969 by Charles S. Rooks-Voter Education Project, Inc. 1970 (Box 27)
  - Literature of Heritage, A Bibliography National Council of Negro Women, Inc. (Box 27)
  - V.E.P. News Voter Education Project-Southern Regional Council, Inc. 1969 (Box 27)
  - Ghetto Power in Action National Urban League 1969 (Box 27)
  - North Carolina Historyland 1964 (Box 27)
  - Mayors of America's Principal Cities U.S. Conference on Mayors July 1973 (Box 27)
  - 4-H College Scholarships and Home Improvements Awards Sperry and Hutchinson n.d. (Box 27)
  - Information About Publicity, Fund Raising Clinics and Club Activities Workshops Sperry and Hutchinson Co. n.d. (Box 27)
  - MFA Insurance Almanac 1966 (Box 27)
  - Anciet Africa by John M. Weatherwax n.d. (Box 27)
  - Narrative of Sojourner Truth n.d. (Box 27)
  - Nat Turner by Thomas Wentworth Higginson n.d. (Box 27)
  - African Explorers of the New World by Harold G. Lawrence n.d. (Box 27)
  - Man Who Stole a Continent by John M. Weatherwax n.d. (Box 27)
  - Races of Mankind by Ruth Benedict and Gene Welftish n.d. (Box 27)
  - Economic Research Services n.d. (Box 27)
  - Quick Facts on the Negro Market for Life Insurance National Insurance Association n.d. (Box 27)
  - How do you Sell to Urban Consumers Ebony 1966 (Box 27)
  - To Prevent a Chain of Super-Watts Alfonso J. Servantes, Harvard Business Review (Box 28)
  - Chicago Sun-Times Sunday Supplement May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Arlington News (Box 28)
  - Pacifica Radio-NOW! publication (Box 28)
  - Proud Heritage (Box 28)
  - A. Philip Randolph: Labor's Grand Old Man-reprint from May 1969 (Box 28)
  - University of Virginia News Letter(on Virginia and politics) 1969 (Box 28)
  - Southern Education Report May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Anciet Africa publication series (John Weatherwax) (Box 28)
  - WBAI-FM Profile of a Station 1968 (Box 28)
  - First Research Company, Banks, Savigs and Loan Associates brochures (Box 28)
  - On the Track Association of American Railroads (Box 28)
  - Now Reporter Newsletter of the Neighborhood Organization of Watts May, 28, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Bob Dylan, Malcom X WPFJ FM publication (Box 28)
  - Know Your Rights Voter Education Project, Southern Regional Council (Box 28)
  - V.E.P. News Voter Education Project June 1969 (Box 28)
  - Republican Battle Line American Conservative Union June, August 1969 (Box 28)
  - Virginia Union Bulletin Founders Day Issue Feb. 1969 (Box 28)
  - Congressional Black Caucus, 2nd National Banquet June 1972 (Box 28)
  - Second Baptist Church, Richmond, Virginia June 1972 (Box 28)
  - Profiles of Virginia's Planning Districts Virginia Division of State Planning and Community Affairs 1973 (Box 28)
  - Dimension USA...Commitment: Environment Ecology Services Bureau, Inc. n.d. (Box 28)
  - Cornerstone Project 1967 (Box 28)
  - Congressional Candidate's Urban Issues Portfolio National League of Cities United Conference of Mayors 1969 (Box 28)
  - Total Community Involvement-Image Development n.d. 1968 (Box 28)
  - Good Neighbors to Our Scout Brothers Boy Scouts n.d. (Box 28)
  - Action '71 Philadelphia Urban Coalition 1971 (Box 28)
  - Summary of Proceedings National Conference on Housing: Regional Issues and Strategies-National Service to Regional Councils 1971 (Box 28)
  - East St. Louis The End of a Decade by Jane Altes-Southern illinois University at Edwardsville 1970 (Box 28)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies' Guide to Black Politics 1972-Part 1. The Democratic National Convention 1972 (Box 28)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies' Guide to Black Politics 1972-Part 2. The Republican National Convention 1972 (Box 28)
  - Federal Review of Voting Changes-How to Use Section 5 of the Voting Rights Act 1974 (Box 28)
  - FOCUS vol. 1 no. 3 January 1973 (Box 28)
  - Federal Drug Abuse Programs JCPS Public Policy Series 1972 (Box 28)
  - Black Community and Revenue Sharing JCPS Public Policy Series 1973 (Box 28)
  - Children and Lead Poisoning JCPS Public Policy Series 1972 (Box 28)
  - Southern Black Mayors Local Problems and Federal Responses by Kenneth S. Colburn 1973 (Box 28)
  - National Roster of Black Elected Officials v. 2 May 1975 (Box 28)
  - Atlantic issue on Republican Party April 1966 (Box 28)
  - JET What Goldwater's Nomination Means to U.S. Negroes July 1964 (Box 28)
  - JET July 22, 1965 (Box 28)
  - JET August 14, 1969 (Box 28)
  - JET August 21, 1969 (Box 28)
  - JET August 20, 1969 (Box 28)
  - JET August 28, 1969 (Box 28)
  - JET November 22, 1982 (Box 28)
  - Newsweek issue with Politics 66 with Reagan on cover March 28, 1966 (Box 28)
  - Newsweek issue: Report from Black America, A Newsweek Poll June 30, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Newsweek Apollo 11 July 21, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Newsweek Apollo 11 on Moon July 28, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Soul Illustrated Winter 1968 (Box 28)
  - Harambee black newspaper December 1967 (Box 28)
  - LA RAZA newpaper June 7, 1968 (Box 28)
  - LA RAZA newspaper May 11, 1968 (Box 28)
  - Parents' Magazine and Better Homemaking September 1968 (Box 28)
  - James Brown Salute 1968 (Box 28)
  - Time Life Books Special Report, The Young Americans 1966 (Box 28)
  - Chicago Sun-Times Tuesday Magazine June 1969 (Box 28)
  - Sepia June 1969 (Box 28)
  - Ebony March 1973 (Box 28)
  - Life Magazine Supplements-Negro History n.d. (Box 28)
- Series VI--Ephemera and photographs 1940s-1970s
  - GOP Tie (Box 29)
  - GOP Wooden Elephant (Box 29)
  - Audio Tape labeled Speech by George Romney on Open Housing (Box 29)
  - Audio Tape labeled Reading Lesson (Box 29)
  - Audio Tape labeled Clarence Townes Impact (Box 29)
  - Audio Tape labeled Governor C. Kirk, Florida, March 2-3 From the People 1968 (Box 29)
  - Audio Tape unlabeled (Box 29)
  - Box of National Negro Republican Assembly membership cards (Box 29)
  - Pocket Day Timer Monthly Calendars for months July-December 1966, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Pocket Day-Timer Monthly Calendars for months February 1967, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Negative image on wooden block of Townes, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Letter Opener, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Armstrong High School Yearbook 1944, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Guest Book (unidentified event), Oversize (Box 30)
  - Copy of Net Testament presented by the Army of the United States, World War II, Oversize (Box 30)
  - Box of business cards of various individuals, Oversize (Box 30)